Guide to the New York Taxi Workers Alliance Records WAG.319
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series III: Administrative, Bulk, 1998-2010; 1972-2012
  - Office Technology Projects, circa 2005 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Organzing Committee, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Organzing Committee Meetings, 2004-2005 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Organizations: Alliance of South Asian American Labor (ASAAL), 2010 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Organizations: American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL–CIO), 2006 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Organizations: Asian American Network for Cancer Awareness, Research, and Training, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Organizations: Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Organizations: Black Radical Congress, Dec 1998 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Organizations: Coalition for the Human Rights of Immigrants, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Organizations: Communist Party USA (CPUSA) 29th National Convention, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Organizations: Endorsements, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Organizations: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 2002 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Organizations: General, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Organizations: New York Immigration Coalition: City Advocacy Day, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Organizations: International Association of Transportation Regulators: Conference, Sep 2006 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Organizations: Jobs with Justice, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Organizations: Jesuit Volunteer Corps, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Organizations: Labor Party, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Organizations: Leadership for a Changing World, 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Organizations: Leadership for a Changing World: Award, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Organizations: Local 375 Civil Service Technical Guild: Hand Scanners, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Organizations: Metropolitan Taxicab Board of Trade (MTBOT): Letter to the Commissioner, Nov 2001 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Organizations: National Cancer Institute, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Organizations: National Immigration Law Center, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Organizations: National Immigration Law Center: Real ID Act, May 2005 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Organizations: National Taxi Workers Alliance, Apr 2012 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Organizations: New Directions, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Organizations: New York City Coalition: Smoking, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Organizations: New York Community Trust, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Organizations: New York Immigration Coalition, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Organizations: New York Joint Action Committee, circa 1998 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Organizations: New York State Federation of Taxi Drivers: The Fair Plan, Jun 2003 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Organizations: People Power: Meeting Notes, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Organizations: Press, 2004-2006 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Organizations: Public Employee Fund: Stop Workplace Violence, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Organizations: Sanctuary for Families, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Organizations: Services Employees International Union (SEIU), 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Organizations: Services Employees International Union (SEIU): Bread and Roses Cultural Project, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Organizations: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC), 2006-2007 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Organizations: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Bill Orleans Ejection Arrest, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Organizations: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Contracts, circa 2005 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Organizations: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Handbook, circa 2000 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Organizations: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Meetings, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Organizations: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Policies and Meetings (I), 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Organizations: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Policies and Meetings (II), 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Organizations: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Proposed Regulations, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Organizations: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Rulemaking, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Organizations: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Rulemaking Agenda, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Organizations: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Rules, 1995-2000 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Organizations: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Website, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Organizations: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Taxi Unions, 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Organizations: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Unions, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Organizations: United Spinal Association: Taxi for All Campaign, Aug 2004 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Organizations: Urban Justice Center: Community Development Project, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Organizations: Urban Justice Center: Survey Results, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Organizations: Wheels of Justice, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Organizations: Work Fairness, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Outreach to Taxi and Limousine Commission, 1997-2001 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Personnel Handbook, Aug 2003 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Political Outreach, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Publications: Domestic Dignity, Jun 2010 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Publications: Legal Bulletin, circa 1999 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Publications: Little India, Jun 1996 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Publications: Related Organizations, 2000s (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Publications: Shift Change, 1998-2012 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Publications: Taxi Insider, 2001-2004 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Publications: Taxi Insider, 2006-2010 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Publications: Taxi Limousine Coach, 2002-2005 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Publications: Taxi Talk, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Safety: Evans Robberies, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Safety: Schaller Reports, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - South Asian Workers, Jun 2004 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Tehran, 2006-2008 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Taxi 07 Design Trust for Public Space, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Taxi 07 Roads Forward, Feb 2008 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Taxis for All, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Unfare: Taxi Drivers and the Cost of Moving the City, Sep 2003 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Department of Labor: Distribution Packet, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Vehicle Safety, circa 2005 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Where We Live and Vote Map, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Worker Centers, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Workers Compensation, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Workplans, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Series IV: Archived Website, May 6, 2011-ongoing
  New York Taxi Workers Alliance, founded in 1998, consists of 15,000 members of yellow taxicab drivers. NYTWA provides legal, health and financial services and improve working conditions through organizing, political and media advocacy, litigation, direct legal services, and access to healthcare. They are part of the Central Labor Council and the International Taxi Workers Alliance. The website contains information on current campaigns, membership information, press releases, event listings, and a blog.